well uh hello everyone so welcome to uh today's
uh magnets uh seminar um i'm filling in for greg
today in case you're not familiar with this face
um so if you're new to magnets uh it starts with
these uh 30 minute presentations um i'm during it
we ask that you keep your microphones muted just
so everyone can hear the presenter we found that
if you're having bandwidth issues and the quality
is poor sometimes it helps to turn off your own
video make sure that you're muted and that can
improve it uh following the the presentation
there'll be a a question discussion period
for 10-15 minutes or so if you don't want to uh
voice your questions over chat uh um or over the
microphone you can always use the the chat feature
and zoom you can type it out and especially if you
add no mic to the uh to the little text chat then
uh one of the conveners will read it out for you
um you know we're still doing everything remotely
um lots of people are still working at home
life goes on so feel free to leave if you
have to leave just you know just get up and go
and since these seminars are going
to be recorded you can always catch
the rest of it online and and just yes as a
reminder these are recorded so um if you you don't
want to kind of be part of that you just keep your
camera off and keep your microphone muted and then
um after the the discussion period there'll be
a bit of a time for like a bit of a social um
kind of just a catch up and that's not going to be
recorded and hopefully it's just a nice chance to
see how people are doing and so without much
more delay uh we're really excited to present um
claire nichols from from oxford now and uh
she'll be talking about uh paleomagnetic
record in uh palisades which i'm excited to
see so i'm gonna hand it over to you claire
wow thank you very much um
just showing the screen um
can you all see that on the laser pointer good
it looks great um okay hi everyone thank you
very much for being here whatever time of day
it is with you um so today i want to talk
to you guys about um kind of a very long
term project this is something i've been
working on since i was an undergrad um
so basically looking at parasite meteorites
their paleomagnetic record and what that can
tell us about their parent body um
so this is kind of all of the data
i've collected in the last i don't know seven
years or so um and thanks to lockdown um
last year i was stuck in my parents living
room and finally had time to kind of sit down
run some models and try and make sense of it all
and what we can say from it um so i'll try and
kind of briefly go through through the paper
that's just been just been published into our
planets if you want to get into the details um
but kind of give you an overview of that today
um okay so to start with my screen go forward
um so just a little overview of actually what a
palace like meteorite is for those that are
not so familiar um the world of meteorites
so they're these really really
beautiful stony iron meteorites
um and they basically just consist of polybean
crystals in an iron matrix so they're very very
distinctive and very kind of simple in terms
of their allergy and for a long time people
thought that they were representative of the
core mantle boundary that makes a lot of sense
for it because they're this intimate mix of
metal and silicates so that's very intuitive
but then astrophysiomagnetists kind of got
involved and ruined that idea um and so the
reason that we no longer think this can be true
is because obviously to be driving a dynamo
and a magnetic field within the parent body you
have to have this molten metallic core that's
vigorously convecting and so if the parasites
were from the poor mantle boundary they'd have to
be below their curie temperature so below kind of
500 celsius and right next to that convecting core
so you'd have way too big a temperature gradient
there um and it doesn't really make much sense
so we now think that not from the hormonal
boundary um and so in the last decade there
have been quite a lot of ideas of how they
might have formed if this this isn't the answer
so one idea that's been put forward is that
they could impact melt um so if you have a
collision between two planetesimals they're
both differentiated um you could inject some
poor materials from one into the mantle of the
other and that might give you this kind of texture
um it's also quite recently been argued
that there could be um kind of evidence of
incomplete differentiation um so if you have
a metal trap within the older being grains
that can't percolate through to the floor then
that could explain some of the textures we see
or it could be some combination of two so
you could have incomplete differentiation
and an impact and that could explain why we see
so much variation in the textures in terms of
sometimes imagine interconnected sometimes the
olivine is sometimes the olivines are rounded
sometimes they're um so there's lots of kind of
textual complexity that we need to understand
and then again quite recently it's been suggested
that actually if the inner core is liquid and the
outer core is solid um then you could actually
have a sulfur-rich metallic dikes coming up um
from within the core and intruding into the mantle
and these metallic dyes would then incorporate all
of you um and that would be worrying about
this texture um and this is something that's
of particular interest at the moment because
this might be what psyche um looks like this
is an asteroid that there's an estimation to
um in the next couple of years which we think
is mostly metallic but have a thin mantle um so
it might be it might be a good analogy for that
okay so how do we fit into all of this um
so my talk's kind of in four sections um and
i'm going to start by talking about the different
paleomagnetic approaches we've used over the years
um to try and actually extract paleo intensities
from the parasites and then i will talk about how
we use that paleo intensity record
to constrain the thermal evolution
and pass that parent body and then
i will finish by discussing whether
any of those models for parasite formation
make sense with pain intensity records
okay so i've used basically two approaches
um to look at paleomagnetism in parasites
the first is kind of a more standard one
in terms of looking at olivine crystals and
magnetic inclusions within them so fancy
critical failure intensity approaches um
and then the second is looking at these
microstructures that form um in the metal so i'm
sure some of you have heard me bang on about the
cloudy zone for years and years and years i'm not
going to go into details of what it is right now
we can talk about that after you're interested um
but essentially there's very very magnetically
stable regions within the metal um this
so we've studied five parasites um all from the
main group so they're all chemically similar
and we think they all come
from from the daily parent body
and the size of the microstructures that form um
in the metal is an indicator of how quickly using
these meteorites so we have a range of cooling
rates from three degrees celsius per million
up to around seven and a half um so the real
thing here to note is that all of these cooling
rates are extremely slow um so even a small
difference of one degree per million years is
a massive difference in actually when these
things reach the same rotating temperature
and so by using these differences in cooling rate
so here i'm showing you a temperature versus time
plot so the gradient of each of these lines
um is basically corresponds to cooling rate um
means that they reach the retaining
blocking temperature so that's the
the inclusions in the olivines um and
the tetrahedra ordering temperature
which is where the cloud design requires
a magnetic field each of the parasites
will reach these temperatures at a different
time and give us this time resolved record
so i can now show you what this record
looks like so now i've got paleo intensity
and micro tesla on the y-axis and then
on the x-axis we've still got time
and when each of our five parasites has recorded
so the first study that was done on the
parasites was done by the rochester group
and john tardino back in 2012 and they
um primarily focused on the magnetic
inclusions within the old bean crystals and
they recovered really really quite intense
paleo intensities and so that was the first study
that said hang on guys actually this thing has an
active dynamo um so really they were the first
ones to spoil the hormonal boundary origin idea
so that got us interested and this was actually
um work i did my masters um back a long time ago
um and so we were trying to use a new technique to
actually get paid intensity from the cloudy zone
and so we thought this was the perfect
opportunity to try and calibrate the two so
we had player intensities from the olivines
now let's see if we get something similar
um and you can see that we have good
agreement between these intensities
um i then went on to measure martin luther and
brennan which have an earlier record and they
fall below this horizontal dash line um which is
basically the the minimum payout intensity that
we can distinguish from zero things so these
are basically within zero it doesn't look like
one thing particularly um profound in terms of
a strong paleo intensity and then finally um i
kind of filled in the gap in the middle and
measured spring water again the cloud zone
um and got an intensity of around 20 microtesla
and the thing you'll probably notice here is
the fact that the error bars for spring water are
significantly smaller than they are fitting like a
scale this is much much better constrained um and
the reason for that is because we've significantly
improved and developed our method for actually
extracting failure intensities from the cancer
only means so again i'm not going to go into this
in a huge amount of detail um but the method we
use is xp which is x-ray photoemission electron
microscopy so it's a synchrotron technique
um and essentially what it allows us to do
is image the direction of magnetization um
in a polished metallic surface um so we get
these red white and blue maps the cloudy zone
is this natural region here and then what
we do is we measure how the magnetization
directions are distributed um within
that field and we see if we have a bias
um so any bias is telling us that the cloud zone
grew in the presence of a external magnetic field
so previously what we did was we measured one
orientation and we got one seven histogram sound
and that only allows you to partially constrain
how strong the field was you only get the minimum
estimate on the paleo intensity by doing that um
so that's why the error bar's been like in a
skeleton big because we don't know how close
to the true failure intensity we were measuring
we just know that they have recorded a field
so now what we do is measuring three
orientations all about 120 degrees apart
and that allows us to fully resolve um the rem
magnetic field vector from maps um so we can
calculate the intensity for each orientation and
we can use that to fully constrain the intensity
and the other nice thing that we can now do
is actually resolve the direction so we can
now convince ourselves that the field that we're
measuring in the character zone is unidirectional
so that's kind of a very brief overview of
what we've done with cloudy zone pale intensity
um but then i wanted to talk a bit about why are
we bothered to use the synchrotron method um and a
kind of a new technique um when we've got olivines
which would measure in a much more standard way
um than magnetic inclusions um and so we've we've
also done this um and my motivation for doing this
really was um again it gives us this independent
calibration um on our synchrotron technique
um and we can use much more familiar approaches
so we can use tele-italia experiments um and heat
these samples up and recover um the intensity
so it's kind of much more familiar ground
and because the magnetic carriers in
the honor beans are slightly different
um it actually means they record before the
cloudy zone so if we get a record from the olivine
and the metal then that increases the resolution
we then have ten data essentially instead of five
so we're trying to do um af demagnetization um
on samples of spring water and inner collar beans
and this is actually one of the best cider
belts i've got so there are there are there
are resolvable components um but you can see
that they're actually completely demagnetized
at really quite low alternating fields so around
20 micro tesla yes from all the stable signal in
these samples and here i'm plotting up the low
coercivity and high capacity components in blue
and red and the spring water and for imalac
and you can see that we couldn't get anything
that looked unidirectional these are really
really unstable um very difficult to interpret
so af experiments didn't really work and again
we tried to do fidelity tests so applying a known
laboratory field um and then basically seeing if
we could if we could extract that paleo intensity
again um so if these were ideal recorders
they all sit along this black line that's
the one-to-one relationship um and
you can see they're kind of all over
the place so none of them uh really meet
our fidelity criteria which would mean
they would sit in this great box um they start
to for very very strong fields of 200 microns
so we quite quickly realized that af demagning
these samples was not going to give us any results
um so then we tried more standard techniques
um so we did some easy tele-atelier experiments
in a controlled atmosphere um so we're doing this
in kind of a standard poly magnetic oven um with
a co2 h2 atmosphere to control the fugacity um
and as you can see um this is our ai diagram
um they alter spectacularly um so
our pcrm checks these triangles
sit over these points here they're miles
away and it's trending in the wrong
wrong direction um and if you look at
the zydefells then you're seeing that
actually the points are romping off in the
direction of the applied laboratory field
um so this is very clearly altering even though
we're measuring it in a very reduced atmosphere um
and actually that was probably the problem
the fact that our atmosphere was so reducing
um so i did some rock magnetic studies on the
samples before and after heating and before this
is irm acquisition so we see we have a population
of fairly low currency grains and then a smaller
heat and slightly higher peritocy grains whereas
after heating um the peaks completely changed and
you actually have much much higher coercivity
carriers post heating and again with the
hysteresis behavior it's very unstable prior to
heating and after heating we're getting nice kind
of single domain carrier signals um so that was a
bit bit suspicious for us about what we were doing
and so we used a quantum dynamics microscope
at harvard um just to have a quick image of
the heated olivines and we kind of found what we
thought we expected um that the magnetization is
focused along the cracks um and when we kind
of zoomed in on the cracks using the sem we
essentially find that they're packed full of new
little iron nipple um grains so we're basically
cooking in um ideal paleo magnetic recorders
um because the conditions are essentially
too reducing um so um and yeah this is just the
compositional maps just showing that it is that
basically an equal amount of iron nickel and not
much sulfur so the control atmosphere experiments
work very well um so i then went to the rochester
lab um to use the same system that they used um
study which is a bit different um
because rather than heating the samples
in a paleomagnetic furnace you heat them
using a laser and the benefit of this method
is the fact that you have much much quicker
heating and cooling times um so you can heat
and cool a sample in five minutes rather than
heating and cooling over two or three hours um
and we were starting to get actually relatively
promising results um but i was only there for
about 10 days and so i kind of looked at a few
samples whereas the work that went into the
2012 study took years um and so i think the main
issue is the fact that you really need to have
the most ideal olivines you really need loads of
samples loads of time using lots of measurements
to recover these they will record um so just a
quick sum up of kind of these two paleomagnetic
approaches and good bits and bad bits of
each um so the benefit of using the olivines
is that we have a paleo intensity approach that we
understand very well um if you can get nice tell
you tell your results um from olivier's in the
parasites then you have a record you can trust
um but it's very very difficult to recover these
records um because of problems with alteration um
and the experiments take a long time and they're
really really challenging i mean popping out kind
of oriented olivines from these samples is um yeah
it takes a lot of time and it's not easy to do
um so the cloudy zone um and using our
synchrotron technique has has some benefits
in the sense that the sample preparation is
much easier you just need a polished surface
and there's no issues with alteration
because there's no heating required
um but obviously it requires applying for a
synchrotron beam time and we're still learning
exactly how to calibrate these paleo intensities
we're much more confident in the numbers we're
getting now than we were a few years ago um
but it's still it's still a very novel method
um so i think doing both was the best thing we
could possibly do seeing seeing how reliable um
okay so that's a whirlwind tour of um of kind of
all the painting and magnetic side of the project
and now for kind of the more interesting bit which
is saying now we've got this time resolved record
um how can we use this to try and constrain
the thermal evolution of parasite parent body
so taking you back to this paleo intensity versus
time plot that i showed you a bit earlier um and
then this is our cloud zone failure intensity
for each of our palestine samples again um
and so the constraint that this really gives us is
the fact that we're assuming we have dynamo off um
when marginal arsenal brenham acquired zero
magnetic field and then we have a dynamo
driven by core convection when spring water
in lac and acquire their magnetic field record
and so the simplest assumption to make here
about why you have two samples that don't
require a field and then three that do is that
um larsen and brenham acquired a magnetic field
before the corps began to solidify um so you don't
have a driving mechanism um for that convection
and then as soon as the course starts to solidify
you can have compositional convection and that's
driving a magnetic field when these three um
when you acquire their magnetic field record
so that's given me two constraints one is that i
know that core crystallization has to happen at
some point between um this intensity record and
this one and then the second one is i know the
core has to be at least partially liquid um while
all three of these apply the magnetic field record
so those are the two constraints
that i used um for my thermal models
so i'll just briefly discuss what
these standard models look like
um so these are kind of the assumptions that
we we've made to keep the models simple so i'm
assuming the parent body um fully differentiated
um and that is we basically start our models when
um the the mantle silicone mindfulness is
solid and the surface is held at 250 kelvin so
the surface is cold the mantle is solid core is in
the middle and then we let it cool by conduction
so keeping everything really as simple as we
possibly can here it's a very first order approach
um and this is what one of the models looks
like so um this is the surface the parent
body and then this is going down to
the center of the planet down here
and then this is basically time going along
along the x-axis and it's color-coded in
terms of its its temperature so the hormonal
boundary is shown by this dotted line here
essentially what we do is we let the planet
cool we know based on their cooling rates um
and when they have acquired their
magnetic record when each of our samples
um should have acquired remnants and so our
constraint is that the pawn needs to begin to
solidify between this point and this point which
represents dynamo off and then dynamo on um and
then the core can't reach this point where it's
completely solid um until after this final call in
so i ran lots of different models um lots of
different configurations of the parent body to see
um in how many situations i could
basically meet these conditions
um and then once i've met the conditions um for
when the core was crystallizing i then also ran a
simple dynamo model um so assuming that we've got
kind of inner core nucleation so the same as what
we have on earth and that the solidification
of the inner core is driving a dynamo
um and for each thermal model i also
produce a paleo intensity versus time curve
that would correspond to what the dynamo
field would look like through time
um and then essentially for the next plot i'll
show you what you'll see is i'm showing average
painting intensity so rather than having this
time resolved curve i've just taken the average
intensity while the dynamo is active with the
overlapping time theory and so that's what
i'm showing on this plot here um i've got my my
maximum average intensity for my dynamo model um
versus the time it would take before to solidify
so essentially it's my dynamo model constraint
versus my thermal model constraint um and then for
each model that i ran um it's varying in terms of
its its sulfur content um and so that's basically
just dictating when the core begins to fluidify
um and so this is the corresponding plot for
body size um so it's showing me the size of the
overall body radius and then the pool size here
and then i'll just quickly show you um a few sort
of results um that i got for each dynamo model
and kind of how i how they um they passed my
criteria i guess and for explaining the data
so this is an example down
here this point number two
um so fairly small core and parent
body um and a high sulfur content um
and for this one the thermal model works in terms
of when the course of the device but the dynamo
model um doesn't because we have two weak pay
intensities and they aren't sustained for long
so again i have other examples where i get kind
of the right intensities but they're not sustained
long enough um sometimes they're too strong
and much too early and then it switches off
and then in some cases they get a record that
actually fits all of my pending intensity data um
quite nicely and so overall the thermal models
i ran it's actually only these four um that gave
me dynamo corresponding dynamo models that have
similar failing sensor trends to the data and so
for all of these i've got a fairly large parent
body with a fairly large pore and relatively low
sulfur contents so that was kind of good and a
great starting point but what you'll notice is
that it's only just explaining the paleo intensity
yeah so it's the lower end of what in like a scale
may have recorded um and if you remember then
actually the parasite olivines sit up here um from
that arduino 25 study so these are still too weak
um to explain kind of all the data sufficiently
so that got me thinking okay if this isn't quite
the right answer to explaining all the data um how
might i be able to get stronger period intensities
and the three simplest ways of increasing the
paleo intensity um is to put parasites closer to
the source of magnetic field generating region
um having a shorter solidification time um so
the longer the dynamo has to be um active for
the less field it can it can generate um or having
a larger pool so if you have a large floor you
have more energy to generate in strong foods so
this is basically telling me that i needed quite
a thin mantle and quite a large core if i was
going to explain all of those paleo intensities
so for those dynamo models i was showing you i
was thinking about kind of the classic case of
um having a solid inner core that's um growing
concentrically outwards like we have on earth
um but then it actually becomes much easier to
explain the parasites um if you also consider
inward crystallization because if the outer core
is actually the solid part and it's the inner core
that's the convection region you can put the
parasites much much closer to the core because
they're not next to the liquid part so that
temperature gradient becomes lesser than the tube
um and you also have much more control found over
the cooling history and how long you have to um
this mechanism so this is the thermal model i've
already shown you um outward crystallization
and then i ran similar models um but in with
crystallization so at this point of course you
need to slid by at the horizontal boundary
and then it solidifies towards the center
and you'll see here the main difference is i've
got a much smaller mantle in this case and the
palace sites have all acquired their magnetic
field records much closer together um than in
this case where they're much much more spread out
um so it just gives me kind of more parameters to
be able to play with by considering both scenarios
um so there's a lot going on on this plot and so
i'll try and kind of explain um everything briefly
so um on the y-axis i have minimum dynamo duration
so that's the minimum time required for
it to have um catch the magnetic field um
record of spring water and in a scale and then
on the x axis we've got the mantle's thickness
and then the size of these points um corresponds
to the thighs and core so big points or a big core
and smaller little core um and then outward
force notification like we have on earth
shown in red and then inward
solidification shown in
um so essentially um just what this shows you
is that if you have outward crystallization
you've got to have quite a large
mantle um thermal model that works
and so the parasites are quite spread out in space
um and in terms of the time of acquiring a record
whereas for inward crystallization you have a much
thinner mantle and you can actually squeeze them
all together and still have core crystallization
at the right time but they they will have pooled
in very very quick succession um within the mantle
so this is kind of interesting because if we want
to distinguish between these two if we can date
the parasites um using a cervical um kind of
chronology um then we can start to distinguish
between um which of these is more more likely
but the interesting thing um that i found in terms
of explaining the the stronger paleo intensities
so again here i put paleo intensity on the
y-axis and magnetic thickness on the x-axis
is the the olivine inclusions um that were
measured in 2012 they sit in this yellow box here
um whereas the clarity zone period intensities
that i've measured sit in the green box here so
where the two overlap and all the studies are
in agreement only works if you have a very very
large pore and very thin mantle and actually
the direction of crystallization doesn't seem to
matter so much um so we might be
able to distinguish between these two
using thermoprom but both work in terms of giving
us the much stronger um intensity um over time
so finally does this allow me to actually say
something about what the parent body looked like
and thinking back to those those formation
mechanisms i talked about from the start
um and so the main conclusion to take away
is the fact that um you think the period of
tensions are telling us you've got to have
a large chord thin mantled um parent body
and this is very similar um to what's
being suggested for this pair of volcanism
mechanisms so again here you have a large
core um sulfur rich diets that can then
you know not much over pressure because the
mountain is thin and so they can intrude
into that mantle um and so this mechanism can kind
of explain the textures that we see in parasites
and it can also explain the paleomagnetic record
um so this is kind of indicating perhaps um
inward course notification is more plausible
um if we want to explain both of these things
um and as i mentioned at the start the
reason that this is kind of a particular
interest at the moment is because of the
upcoming mission to the exploring psyche
and so um i just did some kind of
back of the envelope calculations
um just assuming one density for the core and
one density for the mantle of each of my thermal
models i calculated what the density of that plant
estimate would be just to see if they were in any
way consistent um with the densities that have
been observed uh the psyche um and what we find
is that for the plant assessments with very very
large cause the densities are a bit too high um
but actually for a lot of the models um that have
paleo intensities that are consistent with cloudy
zone um they are also a similar density
to psyche um and it's been suggested that
actually parasites might be the kind of material
um we'll see on the surface um of psyche so that
was kind of just a fun kind of you know maybe
maybe at least from that from a similar process
um okay so just to finish up um so in summary
um they might be from from a planet that looks
a bit like psyche um so something which is mostly
metallic but it does still have a silicate layer
um at its surface to distinguish between
inward and outward core solidification
we really need to use something like thermochrome
and having an independent constraint really really
help us to nail down what's happening um on the
parent body and actually how the parasites form
and in my opinion at least i
think fairy volcanism is looking
like a plaudible mechanism and perhaps more
plausible and easier to explain um than having
impact melts and having to actually inject more
material um down from the surface um so thank you
very much for listening to that kind of whirlwind
tour um i'm very happy to take your questions
well thank you claire i was really exciting
talks on some really challenging uh materials
to work with um people want to give
her sort of a virtual applause there's
some um emojis or whatnot and zoom and
otherwise we can open up for questions
uh oh go on
well if uh while we wait for others uh i guess
clara have you started to think about the um
other palace sites besides besides main groups is
that is that on your horizon yeah potentially um i
would really really like to look at eagle station
parasites um there's very few museums that want
to give examples um the other interesting thing
there was actually a study that came out i think
last year that subdivided the main group parasites
in terms of isotropic composition again um
so it actually looks like there might
be two two bodies instead of one
um so i think that's something i'm
kind of interested in looking at is
are they two different um or do
they both look open like so yeah
simon yeah great talk claire thanks um i was just
wondering how this with a thin solid outer core
uh how that kicks off the um the dynamo with
the compositional convection sort of thing
yeah so that's a good question and it's actually
something i kind of dodged around in the sense
that um there's a there's a really good paper
um by jerome neufeld who's a fluid dynamicist
at cambridge um who worked with james bryson
on 4a iron meteorites because they look like
they crystallized from the outside in and it
generated the dynamo um so it's not particularly
well understood exactly how that drives the dynamo
here yet but they've kind of shown mathematically
that it does um so i didn't really try and model
how that dynamo would work i just looked at the
maximum amount of energy the core would have
in that scenario to generate power intensity
um but yeah so i think it's it's kind of still
up for debate exactly how that would work
uh we have a question from um
brayna i hope i got that right
yes yeah so currently i am doing my master with
this main group meteor and parasite and then
i don't know how much i can talk about my data but
uh my data shows something like the camo
site looking thing it's intruding into the
uh thoroughly
formation so uh we only looking at this and like
every s solar material every
nis solar material is interior
it's not so boring so like i'm
wondering what it's going on
yeah okay no that's that's interesting to hear
um because obviously that that is something
you should be able to see right if it is the
sulfur-rich um kind of metallic fluids coming
up from the core and intruding to the mantle
you should see a lot of sulfur-rich material um
in the parasites um so i think that's another
interesting line of evidence that i've not really
thought very much about is looking at these
things um compositionally but that that could
well rule out that mechanism um it just fits very
nicely paleo intensity observations yeah thank you
um you only mentioned it briefly claire
to be fair but um what like under what
conditions do you know what conditions
you get um like incomplete differentiation
yeah so um you would basically get
in complete differentiation if you're
cooling everything too quickly so differentiation
is really efficient if the entire body is molten
then you can very effectively just remove all
the metal um from the silicate and out whereas
if the body forms relatively cold um and you
actually solidify the silicate and you have
um basically olivines that are interconnected
so they're all touching um then depending on
what the dihedral angle is i must confess i cannot
remember my head what it should be or shouldn't be
um but if i think if the angles basically between
the olives are too narrow then the melt can't
percolate through so any metal that's left at
that point just gets stuck um i personally don't
think that is a reasonable explanation for most of
the parasites because anyway you can even see just
in this picture here the metal is interconnected
so there's no reason for it not to percolate
but it does explain kind of small
patches that we see in some parasites
thank you